ZARAH JAMALUDDIN

zarahsafiya@gmail.com 12709 Red Cedar Dr·Euless, TX 76040 · (214) 994-0052 linkedin.com/in/zarahjamaluddin

SUMMARY

I maintain strong organizational and problem-solving skills and am able to communicate with individuals in a respectful and open manner as I have been exposed to several medical shadowing opportunities in the past and have worked in customer service.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin	Bachelor of Science and Arts, Biology	May 2021
	Minor: Business Foundations	,
	Pre-Health Professions Certificate	
	Overall GPA: 3.33	
WORK EXPERIENCE		
Eastern Union – Commercial Real Estate Intern; Remote		June 2020 – August 2020
· Actively called customers to deterr	nine their interest in real estate	
· Worked directly with senior emplo	yees to help facilitate the process of	
underwriting and obtaining a real e	estate loan for customers	
KPMG – Data Analytics Consulting V	February 2020 – May 2020	
	raw spreadsheet data in order to provide	
customers with concise and accura	te business data	
_	ganize data according to the needs of	
the business owners		
	ers regarding product choice using statistics and	
	analytical dashboard and data visualizations	
University Co-Op – Sales Consultant		August 2019 - February 2020
· Consistently exceeded sales goals b		
service and relationship marketing	skills	
· Demonstrated excellent leadership	abilities; trained and served as role model for	
new sales consultants		

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE AND ACTIVITIES

April 9th, 2021 - April 11th, 2021

· Participated in the nationally recognized DataFest competition as a member of an undergraduate team responsible for conducting data wrangling, analysis, and presentation using R statistical analysis

Delta Epsilon Mu, Professional Pre-Health Fraternity - Member

September 2017 - Present

- · Member of the co-ed professional pre-health fraternity dedicated to health education in all fields of medicine
- Participated in various community service activities including fundraising for the charity program, 20/20/20, which serves to provide people in third world countries with low-cost blindness corrective surgeries

Alpha Phi Omega, Service Fraternity – Member

February 2018 - January 2019

- Member of the largest co-ed service fraternity dedicated to service, leadership, and friendship at The University of Texas at Austin
- · Participated in community leadership programs such as in Merit Badge University in which members helped Boy Scouts of America earn merit badges

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills: Excel, PowerPoint, Word, R, Customer Service

Certifications: Microsoft Office

Languages: English, Bengali, Basic Arabic

Interests: Traveling, Healthcare, Computer Science

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Multivariable Calculus

· M408N: Differential Calculus for Science – Fall 2017; Grade received: A

· M408S: Differential Calculus for Science - Summer 2018; Grade received: A

Intro Statistics

· SDS 328M: Biostatistics - Fall 2019; Grade received: A-

Programming

· SDS 348: Computational Biology and Bioinformatics – Spring 2021; Grade received: N/A

· CS 303E: Elements of Computers and Programming – Spring 2021; Grade received: N/A

Business

- · MIS 302F: Foundations of Information Technology Management Fall 2019; Grade received: A-
- · FIN 320F: Foundations of Finance Spring 2020; Grade received: A